Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Records of past presidents Ken Rollins, Rachael Stewart and Carl Linden, 1954-2013; Series 5; 10 Linear Feet
  - Flotilla-Upriver C&O Canal, Dam 4 Williamsport, FT Frederick C&O Commission meeting by Ed Miller, Assn and Commission, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 1, Videocassette 8)
  - C&O Canal film, Circa 1950-1959; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 1, Videocassette 9)
  - C&O Canal "American History's Greatest Walk," n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 2, Videocassette 10)
  - Monocacy, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 2, Videocassette 11)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, TRT 20 min, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 3, Videocassette 12)
  - 1989 Justice Douglas Hike-19 min-(35th annual), Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 3, Videocassette 13)
  - Flooding: The Ultimate Challenge. C&O Canal NHP, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 4, Videocassette 14)
  - C&O Canal Douglas Hike 1994, Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 4, Videocassette 15)
  - Monocacy Elementary Build a Boat, 2006 June 06; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 1, Videocassette 16)
  - H Wolfe: M Frades WAMU talk show (Tape 1 of 2), 1975 June 03; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 1)
  - H Wolfe: M Frades WAMU talk show (tape 2 of 2), 1975 June 03; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 2)
  - H Wolfe Mrs. Bon'es 6 Class E Wiselaw Press Club, 1975 June 12; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 3)
  - Unmarked, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 4)
  - Unmarked, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 5)
  - Unmarked, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2, Cassette 6)
  - Canal Collection, 2009 February; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 1)
  - Monocacy C&O Tom Kozar, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 2)
  - Cactoctin Aqueduct at Lander, 1989 Winter; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 3)
  - Editor Transfer Disc B, 2008 January; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 4)
  - Towpath Draft, 2008 February 28; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 5)
  - C&O Canal 09 pin card Tom Kozar, 2009; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 6)
  - Canal Art Tom Kozar, 2008 September; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 7)
  - Autumn Canal Tom Kozar, 2009 June; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 3, Dvd 8)
  - Tom Kozar shots, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 9)
  - Tom Kozar Monocacy Aqueduct, 2009 July; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 10)
  - Monocacy Tom Kozar, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 11)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct-good Tom Kozar, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 12)
  - C&O Canal 06 Card PawPaw Tom Kozar, 2006; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 13)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct photos, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 14)
  - 2010 Flood aerial photos, Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 15)
  - Mt. Vernon Presentation on Powtomack Canal, 2004; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 4, Dvd 16)
  - Cactoctin Aqueduct Aug 2005 (GEL), 2005 August; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 17)
  - Master copy of Monocacy Aqueduct DVD TRT 20 min, 2008; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 18)
  - C&O Canal Christmas Ball 2008 White House, Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 19)
  - COCA ATP, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 20)
  - COCA 2001-2004 ATP, Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 21)
  - ATP docs: final cys and ATP inserts, 2005 March-2006 June; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 22)
  - Potomac Sojourn Memory Disk, 2005; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 23)
  - Mike Dwyer-articles Civil War in Montgomery County, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 24)
  - 184.5 miles in 8 minutes: 2009 Douglas Thru-Hike, Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1, Dvd 25)
  - Charles F. Mercer packet boat dedication, 2006 September 09; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 26)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct rededication, discs 1 and 2, 2007 May 21; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 27)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct video documentary update, 2005; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 28)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct TRT 20 min, 2008; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 29)
  - Flooding at the C&O Canal, 2010 March 14; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 30)
  - Cactoctin Aqueduct Restoration June-August 2010 (GEL), 2010 August 10; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 31)
  - Old Patomack Trip Aug 2010 photos and report Vicki Dodson, 2010 August; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 32)
  - Come Walk With Me on the C&O Canal Andrei Kushnir, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 33)
  - Video and Song Come Walk with Me on the C&O Canal Andrei Kushnir, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 34)
  - 2009 Thru Hike Group; Sony, me, Carl, Dave; 2010 WCC Group (Barbara Sheridan), 2009-2010; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2, Dvd 35)
  - 14 slides of Monocacy Aqueduct, 1996-1998; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Laminated poster on the Monocacy Aqueduct, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Poster 1)
- Newsletter: Along the Towpath, 1983-2022; Series 6; 1 Linear Feet 2 document boxes
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains issues of the Association newsletter Along the Towpath.
  Related Materials
  Please note that there are early issues of Along the Towpath in the Administration files series (Series 2) listed in folders titled "membership files Along the Towpath" These issues date from 1970-1999.
  - Along the Towpath, 1983 January - 1997 January; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Along the Towpath, 2000 March - 2002 December; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Along the Towpath, 2003 March - 2004 December; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Along the Towpath, 2005 June - 2007 December; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Along the Towpath, 2008 September - 2011 June; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Along the Towpath, 2011 September - 2013 December; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Along the Towpath, 2014 March - 2015 December; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Along the Towpath, 2016 March - 2019 June; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Along the Towpath, 2019 September - 2022 June; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 3)